Hi, and this was some I'll show you how to use manual mode of
cursor editor.
The manual mode is an alternative of edit mode or compile it.
You can use manual mode directly apply, added across multiple files in your code base,
based on your chart prompt.
The edits are applied directly in the editor where you can review them in place,
and accept or decline these changes.
Manual mode works best when you know exactly what to edit,
what files need to be changed.
And you select, write these files or just move them right here.
And you can provide a clear instruction and complete this task.
So let's go through some use cases for manual mode.
You can refactor parts of your React code.
For example, we can ask to refactor some hooks at the word some mistakes.
For example, if you use effect, it has renders, you can ask to fix it.
You can work, for example, some cloth components to functional components using hooks,
if you want to switch to newer version of React.
You can app in new features.
For example, you can ask, add a login form with validation using some specific library
to my application, so it will do it for you.
It, of course, you'll do some draft code.
It's not always ideal, and you always need to review it because it's your responsibility.
I just generate some ideas for you some ready code and you can be accepted or change it so.
But it's your responsibility is the code you use.
You can implement, ask how to implement the dark mode, for example.
You can ask to fix the bugs.
For example, in something crashing your application, you can ask how to fix it.
You'll do the fix.
You can review it.
For example, how to handle an empty state in least component, and if you'll do some routine
as some boring work for you, so you can just need to write the correct prompt and clear instruction.
You can ask to write some unit tests.
For example, when you create a new component, you can specify what libraries you want to use.
And you'll specify a key at this for this component using these libraries.
For example, you can ask a key at this for some specific method of OOC.
You can also ask to improve the performance.
For example, you know the job application slowly built, and you can ask optimize rendering of
largely using some memorization function.
If you, especially if you don't know how the work or is it good use case for them or not,
so you can ask the pilot and he will do so.
You can optimize some API calls to use, for example, syncivate some sugar.
And you can also ask at their own handling when you have a form of some API request.
So there are a lot of use cases.
So you can also ask to add some TypeScript support to your application.
So I'll do some Renee some Big Renaming in your files.
For example, let's do some changes.
I have to ask to provide the actual current rates.
So can you update current rates in my application?
Or a date and current rating application you should or they should set up the rate-specific
currency, okay, blah, blah, blah.
I use the manual mode, add update rate method to the class.
No, I don't want to add update method to the class.
I reject all the changes.
I want to ask he will update exactly this rates.
So you see I wrote more detailed problem.
So it was my mistake.
Just want to show you.
So if you write not clear instruction to him, he'll do something wrong.
So update out rates in this application to actual once exactly in a constructor.
You see there is default rates, reverse rates and there is enumerates and he did an update.
You will see the changes same as we ask what you can reject them or set.
I can also use them right here.
Now also the fun option you can provide the feedback.
If you like it, you can like response.
If you dislike, you can pick dislike and provide the feedback.
And you can use it.
And also if you click three dots, you will see the number of tokens you use.
If you are on a paid plan, so it will be really useful, you will know how much tokens you use.
Oh, I accept this request.
I want to use the actual rates.
Okay, this is the main use cases how we can use a manual mode and see you in the next lessons.